<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd. – Transformer</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/transformer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Transformer on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	  <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/products/transformer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>S11 M 10kV oil immersed transformer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/transformer/s11-m-10kv-oil-immersed-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/transformer/s11-m-10kv-oil-immersed-transformer/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/45.png&#34; alt=&#34;S11-M-10kV-oil-immersed-transformer&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
S11-M series fully sealed oil-immersed power transformer has the advantages of low loss, low noise and high efficiency, which can achieve good energy saving effect and reduce pollution. Compared with the ordinary oil-immersed transformer, the fully-sealed transformer cancels the oil storage tank, and the change of oil volume is automatically adjusted and compensated by the elasticity of the corrugated sheet of the corrugated oil tank. The transformer is isolated from the air, preventing and slowing down the deterioration of oil and insulation aging. , Enhanced operational reliability, maintenance-free normal operation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three-phase oil-immersed distribution transformer produced by our company adopts a new type of insulation structure, which improves the short-circuit resistance capability, and the iron core is made of high-intelligence cold silicon steel sheet. The high-voltage windings are all made of high-quality oxygen-free copper wire, and adopt a multi-layer cylindrical structure, and all fasteners are specially loosened. The product has the characteristics of high efficiency and low loss, which can save a lot of power consumption and operating costs, and has remarkable social benefits. It is a high-paying technical product promoted by the country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S9M 10kV three phase oil immersed fully sealed power transformer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/transformer/s9-m-10kv-three-phase-oil-immersed-fully-sealed-power-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/transformer/s9-m-10kv-three-phase-oil-immersed-fully-sealed-power-transformer/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/6.png&#34; alt=&#34;S9-M-10kV-three-phase-oil-immersed-fully-sealed-power-transformer&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
S9-M-10kV three-phase oil-immersed fully sealed power transformer is different from ordinary oil-immersed transformers. It cancels the oil storage tank, and the corrugated plate heat sink of the oil tank body is used for heat dissipation and cooling. Its elastic expansion and contraction compensates for the volume of the oil. increase or decrease. This series of products is suitable for 10KV, 50HZ power transmission and distribution systems, and can be used for power and lighting in residential areas, commercial streets, industrial and mining enterprises, and rural areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Low loss, significant energy saving&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The iron core is a circular multi-stage, fully inclined three-stage seam lamination structure&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The high and low voltage windings are all wound with oxygen-free copper wire, and the high voltage windings all adopt multi-layer cylindrical structure&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reasonable body structure&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using new components and fasteners&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCB10 10kV resin insulated dry type transformer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/transformer/scb10-10kv-resin-insulated-dry-type-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/transformer/scb10-10kv-resin-insulated-dry-type-transformer/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/46.png&#34; alt=&#34;SCB10-10kV-resin-insulated-dry-type-transformer&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
Resin insulated dry-type transformers are our company&amp;rsquo;s introduction of foreign advanced technology, and independently developed SCB10 and SCB11 series thin-insulated dry-type transformers with fillers. Because the coils are encapsulated by epoxy resin, they are flame retardant, fireproof, explosion-proof, maintenance-free, and pollution-free. , Small size, can be directly installed in the load center. At the same time, the scientific and reasonable design and pouring process make the product less partial discharge, low noise, and strong heat dissipation capacity. It can run for a long time under 125% rated load under forced air cooling conditions, and is equipped with an intelligent temperature controller. Alarm, over-temperature alarm, over-temperature tripping and gate functions, and connected to the computer through the RS485 serial interface, can be monitored and controlled centrally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;①. The high voltage winding is made of enamelled copper wire, and the low voltage winding is made of copper foil. The high-voltage winding is filled with glass fiber felt, poured with imported epoxy resin without filler in vacuum state, and forms a solid whole after curing, with good mechanical strength, small partial discharge and high reliability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;②. Flame retardant, explosion-proof, non-polluting environment, can be installed in the load center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;③. The coil does not absorb moisture, and the iron core and clamps can be operated at 100% relative temperature and other harsh environments after special processing, and no dehumidification treatment is required for intermittent operation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;④.High resistance to short circuit and lightning shock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;⑤. The inner and outer resin insulation layers of the coil are thin, and the heat dissipation performance is good. The cooling method generally adopts air natural cooling (AN). The air cooling system (AF) can be configured for transformers of any protection class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;⑥. Low loss, good power saving effect, economical operation and maintenance-free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;⑦.Small size, light weight, small footprint, easy installation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
