<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd. – Low voltage Complete switch cabinet</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Low voltage Complete switch cabinet on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	  <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GCK type low voltage withdrawable complete switchgear</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/gck-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/gck-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/42.png&#34; alt=&#34;GCK-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
GCK low-voltage switchgear series is called combined low-voltage withdrawable switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear). It is suitable for the power system of AC 50~60HZ, rated working voltage AC 380V, rated insulation voltage 660V, 1600KVA and below distribution transformer as power distribution, power, lighting, reactive power compensation, motor control center, and designed in the standard cabinet The mixed system of fixed scheme and withdrawal scheme can meet the different needs of users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This series of products has high breaking capacity, good dynamic and thermal stability, advanced and reasonable structure, practical electrical scheme, strong series and versatility;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Various program units can be combined arbitrarily, and one cabinet can accommodate more circuits, saving floor space, beautiful appearance, high protection level, safe and reliable, and convenient maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This product complies with the ICE439 standard and the national standard GB7251 &amp;ldquo;Low-voltage switchgear and control equipment&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The frame is made of special-shaped steel, and the three-dimensional plate is used for positioning, and the bolt is connected without welding structure, so as to avoid welding deformation and production stress, and improve the installation accuracy;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mounting holes of the frame and parts change according to the modulus E=25mm;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The internal structural parts are galvanized, and the exterior is sprayed with electrostatic epoxy powder after pickling and phosphating;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the power center (PC) incoming cabinet, the top is the horizontal busbar area, and the lower part of the horizontal busbar area is the circuit breaker room;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The inclination to the vertical plane shall not exceed 5°.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GCS type low voltage withdrawable complete switchgear</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/gcs-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/gcs-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/38.png&#34; alt=&#34;GCS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
GCS series combined low-voltage switchgear (hereinafter referred to as GCS complete switchgear). It is suitable for the power system of AC 50~60HZ, rated working voltage AC 380V, rated insulation voltage 660V, 1600KVA and below distribution transformer as power distribution, power, lighting, reactive power compensation, motor control center, and designed in the standard cabinet The mixed system of fixed scheme and withdrawal scheme can meet the different needs of users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The basic frame of the switchgear is a combined assembly structure, all of which are fastened and connected by screws, plus doors, partitions, brackets, busbars, drawers and electrical components to form a complete switchgear with the following characteristics:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The overall size of the frame and parts and the size of the opening are changed according to the modulus E = 20mm;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since all structural parts of the frame are fastened and connected by screws, welding deformation and stress are avoided, precision is improved, versatility is strong, applicability is good, and it has high mechanical strength, which fully meets the requirements of the switch cabinet. various performance requirements and changes;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the MCC scheme, the interior of the switchgear is divided into three areas (rooms), the busbar area, the electrical equipment area and the cable area, and the three areas are separated by steel plates to ensure the normal operation of the line and effectively prevent the expansion of faults. When the drawer is pulled out of the cabinet, the charged body in the cabinet is not exposed, which is safe and reliable;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the PC scheme, the manual mechanisms of AH and ME circuit breakers protrude out of the door. When operating by hand, there is no need to open the door panel, which is safe and convenient;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the fixed scheme, it not only retains the characteristics of simplicity, practicality and low price of the fixed scheme, but also has the same appearance as a chest of drawers. Its interior is also divided into busbar area, electrical equipment area and cable area. The three areas are also equally It is safe and reliable to separate with steel plate or insulation board, and it is an ideal equipment to replace the old domestic fixed products;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The drawers of the MCC cabinet have four standard sizes, which are 200, 300, 400, and 600 respectively. They are light in structure, easy to assemble, and high in dimensional accuracy. The four standard sizes can be changed according to the design and user requirements. The drawer unit has Good interchangeability, and there are working position and separation position, the handle can be locked by padlock, and it is in the specified disconnection position;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The switchgear is designed for two power supply and consumption types of three-phase four-wire and three-phase five-wire power distribution system. The neutral bus N line and the protective grounding bus PE line are installed on the bottom of the cabinet, and the outlet end is used Busbar connection makes it very convenient for users to connect cables;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to ensure the reliable continuity of grounding, all common parts such as drawer rails in the cabinet are galvanized;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A natural ventilation net cover is provided on the top of the switchgear without reducing the protection level of the enclosure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In short, the switchgear adopts the structure imitating foreign advanced cabinets, with high mechanical strength and high degree of standardization. It conforms to the IEC439 international standard and GB7251 national standard as a whole. Its protection level conforms to IP3X in GB4208 and is equivalent to IP30 in IEC529.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinets can be widely used in power plants, substations, factories and mines and other power users. In the power distribution system with AC 50Hz, rated working voltage 380 V, and rated current up to 3150 A, it can be used as power, lighting and distribution systems. Electric energy conversion, distribution and control of electrical equipment.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/43.png&#34; alt=&#34;GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt; &amp;ldquo;GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet&amp;rdquo;
GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinet is a new type of low-voltage power distribution cabinet designed by our company based on the principles of safety, economy, rationality and reliability according to the requirements of the superiors in the Ministry of Energy, the majority of power users and the design department. The incoming lines include upper, lower, left, middle, right on the top of the cabinet and rear incoming lines to meet the actual needs of various projects for different incoming lines. At the same time, there is a fixed position in the cabinet for power plants and special users to install electromechanical protection and automatic devices. The product has the characteristics of high breaking capacity, good dynamic and thermal stability, flexible electrical scheme, convenient assembly, strong series and practicability, novel structure, high protection level, etc., and can be used as a replacement product for low-voltage complete switchgear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet body of the GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinet adopts the form of a general cabinet, and the frame is assembled by partial welding of 8MF cold-formed steel. quality. The components of the universal cabinet are designed according to the principle of modules, and there are 20 mold mounting holes, the universal coefficient is high, and the factory can realize pre-production. Not only shorten the production cycle, but also improve work efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The design of the GGD cabinet has fully considered the heat dissipation problem during the operation of the cabinet, so there are different numbers of heat dissipation slots at the upper and lower ends of the cabinet. When the electrical components in the cabinet heat up, the heat rises and can be discharged through the slots at the upper end. The cold air is continuously supplemented into the cabinet through the slots at the lower end, so that the sealed cabinet body forms a natural ventilation channel from bottom to top to achieve the purpose of heat dissipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the requirements of modern industrial product modeling design, the GGD cabinet adopts the method of golden ratio to design the shape of the cabinet body and the division size of each part, so that the whole cabinet is beautiful and generous, and has a new look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet door is connected to the frame with a rotating shaft type living hinge, which is convenient for loading and unloading. There is a mountain-shaped rubber-plastic strip embedded in the hem of the door. When the door is closed, the strip between the door and the frame has a certain compression stroke, which can prevent the door from directly colliding with the cabinet body and improve the protection level of the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The instrument door equipped with electrical components is connected to the frame with multi-strand annealed copper wires. The installation parts in the cabinet are connected with the frame by knurled screws, and the whole cabinet constitutes a complete grounding protection circuit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet topcoat is made of polyester orange-shaped baking varnish, which has strong adhesion and good texture. The whole cabinet is in matt tone, which avoids the glare effect and creates a more comfortable visual environment for the staff on duty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The top cover of the cabinet can be removed when necessary, which is convenient for the assembly and adjustment of the main busbar on site. The four corners of the cabinet top are equipped with lifting rings for lifting and shipment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protection level of the cabinet is IP30, and the user can also choose between IP20~IP40 according to the requirements of the use environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GGJ-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/ggj-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/ggj-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/41.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;GGJ-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
GGJ reactive power compensation device is used in the main circuit and branch circuits of the enterprise power system to improve the power factor and avoid the reactive power from the power system, thereby saving electricity costs. The capacitor automatic switching and cutting set device includes a multi-functional automatic power compensation controller, which has multiple functions such as automatic switching of capacitor banks, measurement and display of various power parameters, and output alarm signals. The whole set of automatic power factor improving capacitor device includes BKMJ dry-type capacitor bank, the main structure is directly constructed as each circuit contains capacitors, capacitor-specific SLFK intelligent low-voltage composite switches and high-performance fuses, which will make its maintenance very simple , under the conditions of current resistance allowed by cables or copper bars and switching switches, the capacity of the capacitor bank can be adjusted freely. For larger capacitor sets (more than 300KVAR), it can be divided into multiple cabinets and used in parallel, and each cabinet has its own independent protection system. The complete set of capacitors for low-voltage automatic power factor adjustment can be used for three-phase co-complementation, and can also be designed as a combination of co-complementation and separate compensation according to customer needs to meet various needs of customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The advanced intelligent low-voltage electronic composite switch is used as the switching element, which completely solves the surge problem when the capacitor is switched on. There is no worry of contact burnout, no heat dissipation, and no harmonic injection. It is safe and reliable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;① High precision: The data sampling measurement adopts true effective value, the measurement accuracy of voltage and current reaches 0.5 level, and the measurement accuracy of power factor and power energy reaches 1.0 level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;② Flexible group compensation method: The mixed compensation method of combining three-phase compensation and group compensation, fixed compensation and co-compensation can be set in groups through the control panel, and each group can set its compensation mode and control parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;③ Perfect protection functions: undervoltage protection, overvoltage protection, loss of voltage protection, overcurrent protection, phase loss protection, harmonic protection and other protection measures, with high reliability. The design is reasonable, the structure is simple, the use is convenient, the anti-interference ability is strong, and the technical indicators are in the leading position in China. The standard cabinet is suitable for various occasions and occupies a small space. Simple installation, no impact on production, unattended, maintenance-free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rated voltage: 380VAC 3~; Rated insulation voltage: 660VAC 3~;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated frequency: 50HZ or 60HZ;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compensation method: combination of three-phase compensation and single-phase compensation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compensation capacity: 420kvar~60kvar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compensation mode: cycle switching, coding switching, fuzzy control automatic switching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fastest response time: ≤20ms;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cabinet height: 2000mm, 2200mm;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Width: 600, 800, 1000, 1200mm;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thickness: 600, 800, 1000mm;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protection class: IP30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GZDW Intelligent High Frequency DC Control Panel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/gzdw-intelligent-high-frequency-dc-control-panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/gzdw-intelligent-high-frequency-dc-control-panel/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/36.png&#34; alt=&#34;GZDW-Intelligent-High-Frequency-DC-Control-Panel&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GZDW series DC screen with cadmium nickel battery, floating charger, equipped with automatic detection and alarm device, has long service life, no pollution, convenient maintenance, stable voltage, ultra-low internal resistance output, withstand large current impact and strong adaptability, reliability Advanced features, it is an ideal DC operating power supply device, which can be widely used in substations of 500kV and below and power plants below, and can also be used in metallurgy, mining, petroleum, radio and television, computer rooms, underground railways, high-rise buildings In construction and other departments, it is used as DC control, signal power supply, power failure protection and circuit breaker operating mechanism opening and closing power supply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two-way AC input controlled by microcomputer can be switched automatically;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AC input overvoltage, undervoltage, overcurrent, phase loss and zero automatic detection, display and alarm protection;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The charging and floating charging device adopts intelligent high-frequency switching rectifier module, N+1 redundant combination, automatic current sharing, and can be plugged and unplugged;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The process of battery equalization charge and float charge is automatically switched, and it can operate normally according to the computer settings. Disconnection of the power grid, recovery of power transmission and other procedures realize the intelligent floating charge management of the battery;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the microcomputer control device fails or sends out wrong control commands, the charging module enters an autonomous working state, and the output voltage is the safe voltage set by the factory to ensure the reliability of the system operation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The intelligent four-remote system provides detailed communication protocols for AC input, DC output, battery circuit and expanded environmental monitoring, and has an intelligent interface for communication with the substation integrated automation system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Input voltage: AC380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Output voltage: DC220, 110, 48, 24V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Battery capacity (larger): 3000AH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maximum regular load current: 300A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Control bus accident load current: &amp;lt;300A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accident load time: 8b&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Number of feed-out channels: 4-6Track channels&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Closing bus, closing pulse current: 5000A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Closing pulse time: 0.3h&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Number of feed-out channels: 4-6Track channels&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JXF series wall mounted distribution box</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/jxf-series-wall-mounted-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/jxf-series-wall-mounted-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;JXF (indoor) wall-mounted control box, all products are bent and welded by unbending steel plates, and the surface is electrostatically sprayed with epoxy resin, which is beautiful and durable. The box is equipped with an installation base plate, which can be installed with electrical equipment, and the door can be opened more than 90 degrees and rotated flexibly.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/13.png&#34; alt=&#34;JXF-series-wall-mounted-distribution-box&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Widely used in architectural lighting and small power control circuits of hotels, apartments, high-rise buildings, ports, cars, airports, warehouses, hospitals, factories and mines, etc., suitable for AC 50Hz or 60HZ, AC single-phase AC240V, three-phase AC450V and Below, in indoor lighting and power distribution lines with a current of 250A or less, it is used for line overload protection, short circuit protection and line switching. This type of equipment is suitable for civilian use or places that non-professionals can enter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF (indoor) and JFF (outdoor) distribution boxes are designed and assembled into various control functions according to the type, specification and quantity of components. The size of the box can be selected arbitrarily to achieve a perfect combination of structure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Dimensions: (H&lt;em&gt;W&lt;/em&gt;D) mm&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;dimensions-hwd-mm&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#dimensions-hwd-mm&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;JXF-2520/14，300&lt;em&gt;250&lt;/em&gt;140&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-3520/14，300&lt;em&gt;250&lt;/em&gt;140&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-3520/18，300&lt;em&gt;250&lt;/em&gt;180&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-3030/14，300&lt;em&gt;300&lt;/em&gt;140&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-3030/18，300&lt;em&gt;300&lt;/em&gt;180&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-4030/14，400&lt;em&gt;300&lt;/em&gt;140&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-4030/20，400&lt;em&gt;300&lt;/em&gt;200&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-5040/14，500&lt;em&gt;400&lt;/em&gt;140&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-5040/20，500&lt;em&gt;400&lt;/em&gt;200&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-5040/23，500&lt;em&gt;400&lt;/em&gt;230&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-6040/14，600&lt;em&gt;400&lt;/em&gt;140&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-6040/20，600&lt;em&gt;400&lt;/em&gt;200&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-6040/23，600&lt;em&gt;400&lt;/em&gt;230&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-6050/14，600&lt;em&gt;500&lt;/em&gt;140&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-6050/20，600&lt;em&gt;500&lt;/em&gt;200&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-6050/23，600&lt;em&gt;500&lt;/em&gt;230&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-7050/16，700&lt;em&gt;500&lt;/em&gt;160&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-7050/20，700&lt;em&gt;500&lt;/em&gt;200&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-7050/23，700&lt;em&gt;500&lt;/em&gt;230&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-8060/20，800&lt;em&gt;600&lt;/em&gt;200&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-8060/23，800&lt;em&gt;600&lt;/em&gt;230&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-8060/25，800&lt;em&gt;600&lt;/em&gt;250&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-10080/20，1000&lt;em&gt;800&lt;/em&gt;200&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-10080/25，1000&lt;em&gt;800&lt;/em&gt;250&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JXF-10080/30，1000&lt;em&gt;800&lt;/em&gt;300&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LK DFX301 10 low voltage branch box</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/lk-dfx-301-10-low-voltage-branch-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/lk-dfx-301-10-low-voltage-branch-box/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/8.png&#34; alt=&#34;LK-DFX-301-10-low-voltage-branch-box&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The branch box is divided into two categories according to its electrical composition: one type does not contain any switchgear, and there are only accessories for processing and connecting cable ends in the box. The structure is relatively simple, the volume is small, and the function is relatively&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/9.png&#34; alt=&#34;LK-DFX-301-10-low-voltage-branch-box&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MNS type low voltage withdrawable complete switchgear</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/mns-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/mns-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/39.png&#34; alt=&#34;MNS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
MNS is a modular and multi-functional low-voltage power distribution cabinet, which is used in all low-voltage systems that require high reliability in the fields of metallurgy, petroleum, chemical industry, industrial and mining enterprises, and infrastructure: power distribution box motor control system. The counter structure adopted by MNS has high flexibility. According to the needs of customers or different usage occasions, various types and specifications of components are installed in the cabinet. According to the same electrical equipment, various types of feed units can be installed in the same row of cabinets or in the same cabinet. Such as: feeder circuit and motor control circuit can be mixed together. MNS is a full range of low-voltage switchgear that can meet your all-round needs. Applicable to all low voltage systems below 6300A, MNS can provide a high level of reliability and safety. Humanized design strengthens the protection required for personal and equipment safety. MNS is a fully assembled structure. Its unique profile structure and connection method, as well as its compatibility with various elements, can meet the requirements of demanding construction schedules and power supply continuity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;① In order to facilitate the installation of equipment and on-site construction, a dedicated cable channel is provided in the power distribution cabinet, and corresponding cable fixing parts are attached.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;② Each position of the drawer unit is accurately positioned and clearly indicated. And each position can be locked with up to 3 padlocks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;③The special profile structure and connection method ensure the strength of the cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;④The drawer unit adopts contact wires to be directly plugged in with the L-shaped vertical busbar, which is simple and reliable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;⑤The unique 3-section guide rail makes the drawer in and out more flexible and convenient, and the internal components and wiring can be inspected, maintained or replaced without the drawer unit detaching from the cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PZ30 modularized terminal combined electric appliance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/pz30-modularized-terminal-combined-electric-appliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/pz30-modularized-terminal-combined-electric-appliance/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pz30 modularized terminal combination electric appliance is a new type of product developed in our country in recent years. It is widely used in industrial and mining enterprises, shops, hospitals, stations, ports, high-rise buildings and residential buildings, etc., as a complete set of equipment for circuit power distribution and control, and protects the circuit from overload, short-circuit leakage, and overvoltage Combined electrical appliances It is used in the end circuit of single-phase three-wire or three-phase five-wire with AC frequency 50Hz, rated voltage 220V or 380V, and maximum total load current of 100A.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/12.png&#34; alt=&#34;PZ30-modularized-terminal-combined-electric-appliance&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cabinet has a reasonable structure and a novel shape. It adopts a plastic shell and an open door cover for easy operation. Combined electrical appliances have 2, 4, 6, 8, 10, 12, 15, 18, 20, 24, 30, 36, 40, 45, 60 loops in any combination of various modular electrical components, which are mounted on a H35 standard on the track. The wiring scheme is flexible in combination, can be connected in various forms, and can be connected to the zero row and the ground row.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are two types of installation: surface-mounted (suspended) and concealed-mounted (wall-mounted). Knock-out holes for incoming and outgoing wires are provided on the top, bottom and back of the cabinet to facilitate wiring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The box is made of galvanized wrench, PVC, stainless steel and other materials. The maximum cross-sectional area of the main incoming cable is generally 25mm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XL21 type floor distribution cabinet</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/products/low-voltage-complete-switch-cabinet/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/37.png&#34; alt=&#34;XL-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
XL-21 type power cabinet can be widely used in metallurgy, mining, petroleum, chemical industry, electric power, building materials, mechanical processing, transportation, hotels, restaurants It is used for power distribution and open power distribution of three-phase four-wire power system. It provides protection for overload, short circuit and leakage of the line, and performs normal conversion of the circuit. This product is an indoor closed device, and its enclosure protection level is IP40. The product complies with GB7251.1 and IEC60493-1 and other standards&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The XL-21 type power cabinet is closed and dust-proof, and the shell is made of cold-rolled steel plate, which can be used as a switching power supply. A voltmeter is installed in front of the power cabinet to indicate the voltage of the bus bar. There is a door in front of the power cabinet. , After the door is opened, the equipment inside the cabinet is exposed, which is convenient for inspection and maintenance. The XL-21 type power distribution cabinet adopts new electrical components, which has the characteristics of compact structure, convenient maintenance, and flexible line protection. The power cabinet is equipped with air circuit breaker and fuse as short circuit protection, and is also equipped with Device and thermal relay, the front door of the cabinet can be equipped with indicating electric meter, operation button and indicator light. A busbar box can also be attached to the cabinet, which is suitable for multiple parallel installations. The busbar box is bent and closed with steel plate, and its height is 300 mm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Main circuit rated voltage: AC380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Auxiliary circuit rated voltage: AC220V/AC380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated frequency: 50/60HZ&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated insulation voltage: 660V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated current: &amp;lt;800A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
