<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd. – High Voltage Switchgear Cabinet</title>
    <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in High Voltage Switchgear Cabinet on Linyi Senkuo Electromechanical Co., Ltd.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HXGN15 12 box type fixed AC metal enclosed switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/hxgn15-12-box-type-fixed-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/hxgn15-12-box-type-fixed-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;HXGN15-12 (F), HXGN15-12 (F R) box-type fixed AC metal-enclosed switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear), suitable for rated voltage of 12KV, rated frequency of 50HZ, rated current of 630A and above A three-phase AC system powered by network cabinets or radial terminals, used for segmenting and branching of cable lines. This product is equipped with FLN36-12D type sulfur hexafluoride load switch or FLRN36-12D type load switch-fuse combination electrical appliance with insulating shell, which has the advantages of small size, light weight, easy operation, light operation force, reliable interlocking and maintenance-free. It is a new generation of high-voltage switchgear required for the transformation and construction of urban power grids. The equipment is mainly used as distribution automation system for city power supply load center and cable power supply.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/25.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;HXGN15-12-box-type-fixed-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
The principle of ring network power supply: ring network power supply is generally composed of three basic units. The incoming and outgoing line cabinets are used as the ring network unit. When any line fails, it can be isolated in time, and the other unit maintains the continuous power supply of the certified user transformer branch. The user circuit ring network cabinet plays a role of protection and isolation for the transformer, which is convenient for maintenance and repair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet structure is assembled, stable and reliable, and easy to assemble. It can form a ring network power supply unit and various wiring methods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Small size, light weight, small footprint, easy to install.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ring network cabinet has three safe and independent compartments: the busbar room, the switch room and the instrument compartment. The cabinet body and each component have reliable safety grounding to ensure the personal safety of operators and maintenance workers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ring network cabinet can be equipped with FN12-12D, FN25-12D and other load switches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mechanical interlock is advanced and reliable, fully meeting the requirements of &amp;ldquo;five defenses&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ring network cabinet can be extended arbitrarily, and can be composed of basic units to form a variety of combination schemes according to user requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Five defenses&amp;rdquo; locking function&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Power transmission operation: Only when the cabinet door is closed and locked, and the grounding switch is operated to the &amp;ldquo;open&amp;rdquo; position, can the load switch be operated to the closing position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Power failure operation: When the load switch is in the isolation position, the grounding switch can be closed, and when the grounding switch is in the closing position, the cabinet door can only be opened after the insulating partition is inserted in place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a reliable interlock between the vacuum interrupter and the isolation knife, and the isolation knife and the grounding knife are interlocked with each other and interlocked with the cabinet door, and the insulating partition is also interlocked with the cabinet door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sales@lyskjd.com&#34; &gt;Sales@lyskjd.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HXGN17 12 unit AC metal enclosed ring network switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/hxgn17-12-unit-ac-metal-enclosed-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/hxgn17-12-unit-ac-metal-enclosed-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/24.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;HXGN17-12-unit-AC-metal-enclosed-ring-network-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
HXGN17-12 box-type (fixed) metal-enclosed ring network switchgear (referred to as ring network cabinet) is a new type of high-voltage switchgear produced for the needs of urban power grid transformation and construction. In the power supply system, it is used to break the load current and close the short-circuit current. The ring network cabinet is equipped with a vacuum load switch, and the replacement mechanism is a spring operating mechanism, which can be operated manually or electrically. The switch and isolating knife are equipped with a dry-action operating mechanism. This ring network cabinet has a strong set-up, small size, no fire and explosion hazards, and has reliable &amp;ldquo;five-proof&amp;rdquo; functions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outside of the ring network cabinet is composed of a basic skeleton, a top plate, a panel, and a side plate to form a closed structure. The top of the ring network cabinet is the bus room, and the front of the bus room is the instrument room. The steel plates between the two rooms are separated. The upper part of the cabinet has a load switch room, and the middle and lower parts are cable entry and exit lines and other component rooms. The main equipment of the ring network cabinet It is composed of vacuum load switch, isolating switch (or isolating knife switch with fuse), earthing switch, lightning arrester, operating mechanism, interlocking mechanism and measurement and metering circuit, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ring network cabinet is mainly equipped with FZN21-1212/630 two-position vacuum load switch, and the main scheme is the inlet and outlet cabinets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Incoming line cabinet scheme: a FZN21-12/630 two-position vacuum load switch is installed in the cabinet. The cabinet can also be flexibly equipped with CT and PT, and the main circuit is equipped with a FZN21-12630 vacuum load switch equipped with an isolation knife, which can respectively achieve connecting the busbar and isolating two stations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outlet cabinet scheme: the cabinet is equipped with a FZ8N21-12/T125-1 5 load switch-fuse type combined electrical appliance, and CT, PT and ZnO lightning arresters, fuse combined electrical cabinets, and fuses can be flexibly assembled in the cabinet. The tube is equipped with a striker, and the striker strikes the tripping mechanism in case of a short circuit to realize quick disconnection and effectively protect electrical equipment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Five defenses&amp;rdquo; locking function:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;① Power transmission operation: Only when the cabinet door is closed and locked, and the grounding switch is operated to the &amp;ldquo;open&amp;rdquo; position, can the load switch be operated to the closing position&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;② Power-off operation: When the load switch is in the off position, the grounding switch can be closed, and when the grounding switch is in the closed position, the cabinet door can only be opened when the insulation board is in place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;③ There is a reliable interlock between the vacuum fire chamber and the isolation knife, while the isolation knife and the grounding knife are interlocked with each other and interlocked with the cabinet door, and the insulation partition is also interlocked with the cabinet door&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;④Mechanical interlocking can also be realized between the two incoming cabinets, between the incoming cabinet and the outgoing cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sales@lyskjd.com&#34; &gt;Sales@lyskjd.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HXGN17 40.5 high voltage vacuum ring network switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/hxgn17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/hxgn17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/32.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;HXGN17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HXGN17-40.5 high-voltage vacuum ring network switchgear (hereinafter referred to as ring network cabinet) is a 50Hz AC three-phase indoor high-voltage power distribution equipment. It seals the load switch, grounding switch and the bus bar of the circuit together in a metal shell, adopts a spring operating mechanism, and uses SF6 gas as an arc extinguishing and insulating medium. It is suitable for ring network power supply or dual radiation power supply of 40.5kV power supply line, which can change the original single radiation power supply mode. When the line fails, it can restore the transformer loop feed in time, which greatly improves the reliability and utilization of power supply. It is especially suitable for industrial and commercial areas or rural towns with high power supply load density and cable feeder network. At the same time, the ring network cabinet is safe to use, not affected by the climate, easy to install, less maintenance, and saves space. It is very suitable for installation in box-type substations. , The load switch or load switch-fuse combination in the ring main unit can also be used as a separate cabinet.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/31.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;HXGN17-40.5-high-voltage-vacuum-ring-network-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ring network cabinet is composed of four parts: switch room, fuse room, operating mechanism room and cable room (underframe).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The switch room is composed of various functional circuits (including earthing switch and load switch) sealed in the metal shell and the bus bars between the circuits. The shell is welded by 3mm cold-rolled steel plate (or stainless steel plate). Each functional circuit includes a load switch and a grounding switch. The load switch is composed of a vertically moving moving contact system and a static contact at the lower end. When the switch is closed, the moving contact moves downward and the load switch is turned on. The grounding switch is composed of a moving contact knife and a static contact knife. During the spring movement, the grounding switch is quickly connected. There is a rectangular assembly process hole on the upper and rear parts of the switch room, and an observation window is installed on the front of the ring network cabinet, and the &amp;ldquo;open&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;close&amp;rdquo; positions of the grounding switch can be seen. An explosion-proof device is installed at the rear of the ring network cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The load switch adopts compressed air internal blowing structure, which has strong arc extinguishing ability and does not affect the phase-to-phase and ground insulation. The dynamic and static contacts are equipped with arc contacts, which greatly improves the number of breaking times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fuse and the load switch chamber constitute a transformer protection circuit. The high-voltage current-limiting fuse is installed in an epoxy-cast insulating shell. After the fuse is blown, the striker pops up and the load switch opens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The operating mechanism room is located on the front of the ring network cabinet. In each functional circuit, the load switch is equipped with a manual (or electric) energy storage spring operating mechanism, and the grounding switch is equipped with a manual energy storage spring operating mechanism. There is a They are respectively used for the load switch closing operation and the manual opening rotary knob, the opening and closing operation holes of the grounding switch, the load switch opening and closing position indicator lights and the electric opening and closing buttons, and are equipped with analog lines and switch status Display plate and locked position, load switch and grounding switch are operated with interlocking device to prevent misoperation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Order Notes:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;order-notes&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#order-notes&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following technical information should be provided when ordering:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;· Main wiring scheme number, purpose and single-line system diagram, rated voltage, rated current, rated short-circuit breaking current, layout diagram of power distribution room and layout diagram of switchgear, etc.;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;· Requirements for switchgear control, measurement and protection functions, as well as requirements and schematic diagrams for other locking and automatic devices;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;· The type, specification and quantity of the main electrical components in the switchgear;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the switchgear is used in special environmental conditions, it should be specified in the order;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;· Other special requirements must be explained and negotiated in detail before placing an order.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sales@lyskjd.com&#34; &gt;Sales@lyskjd.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KYN28 12 armored removable AC metal enclosed switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/kyn28-12-armored-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/kyn28-12-armored-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/28.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;KYN28-12-armored-removable-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KYN28-12 type (GZS1) armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear) is a three-phase AC 50Hz indoor complete power distribution device, used to receive and non-distribute 3-12KV network power and The circuit implements control protection and supervision. Various types of microcomputer integrated relay protection devices are installed on the panel of the relay chamber of this product, and can realize the intelligent control of the system. It has the functions of remote control, telemetry, remote signaling and remote adjustment, and is controlled by CAN bus with communication interface. The on-site network also has the functions of preventing misoperation of circuit breakers, preventing pulling back of the handcart with load, preventing grounding switch from being closed with a point, preventing the grounding switch from transmitting power at the grounding position and preventing accidental entry into the charged interval, namely the &amp;ldquo;five prevention&amp;rdquo; functions for short.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet can be equipped with VSI (ZN63), ZN12V vacuum circuit breaker, imported VD4 vacuum circuit breaker and VC series vacuum contactor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shell and partition of the switchgear are made of high-quality imported aluminum-zinc-coated steel plates processed by CNC machine tools and then bolted, so the assembled switchgear can maintain the uniformity in size. It has strong anti-corrosion and anti-oxidation effects, and has higher mechanical strength than the same steel plate. The switch cabinet is divided into handcart room (circuit breaker compartment), busbar room, cable room, relay instrument room (low voltage room) by partitions. Each unit case is independently grounded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet shell and partitions of the switchgear are made of aluminum-zinc-coated steel plates or steel plates processed by CNC machine tools and then bolted after bending, so the assembled switchgear can maintain the uniformity in size. Aluminum-zinc clad steel plate has strong anti-corrosion and anti-oxidation effects, and has higher mechanical strength than the same steel plate. The switchgear is divided into handcart room, busbar room, cable room and relay instrument room by the partition, and the shell of each unit has independent grounding. The parts of the switchgear are all electrostatically sprayed to make the surface have the advantages of anti-collision, corrosion resistance, beautiful appearance (the color can be customized by the user), etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Normal use conditions:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;normal-use-conditions&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#normal-use-conditions&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;◆Ambient air temperature: upper limit temperature +40℃. The lower limit temperature is -15°C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Relative humidity: daily average relative humidity: ≤95%; daily average water vapor pressure not exceeding 2.2KPa;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monthly average relative humidity: ≤90%; monthly average water vapor pressure does not exceed 1.8KPa;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Altitude: below 1000m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Earthquake intensity: no more than 8℃.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆The surrounding air should be free from obvious pollution such as corrosive or combustible gas and water vapor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆No place with severe vibration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆When it is used under the normal conditions specified in GB3906, the user shall negotiate with the company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sales@lyskjd.com&#34; &gt;Sales@lyskjd.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KYN28A 24 type removable AC metal enclosed switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/kyn28a-24-type-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/kyn28a-24-type-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/29.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;KYN28A-24-type-removable-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This product is suitable for three-phase AC 50/60Hz power system, used to receive and distribute electric energy, and to control, protect and detect the circuit. The switchgear has two structural forms: armored cabinet and double busbar cabinet. It can be equipped with SF6 circuit breaker, VD4-24 circuit breaker, ZN72-24 fully insulated vacuum circuit breaker, and the secondary circuit is equipped with advanced and reliable control protection unit. The interior of the product adopts APG epoxy casting and reliable solid fully insulated busbar technology for full insulation design. It has good electric field distribution measures. It is a miniaturized switchgear with advanced technology, stable performance, reasonable structure, convenient use, safety and reliability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;★ The busbar adopts heat-shrinkable insulation material or epoxy-coated insulation means to optimize the shape of the electrodes, so that the cabinet structure is compact and the floor space is reduced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;★ The cabinet body is made of high-quality cold-rolled steel plates and imported aluminum-zinc coated plates, which are formed by CNC sheet metal processing and connected by high-strength bolts, nuts and rivet nuts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;★Insulation boards are installed in the busbar room, handcart room and cable room in the cabinet, which greatly improves the insulation level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;★ It can be equipped with domestic VS1-24 vacuum circuit breaker or Schneider&amp;rsquo;s VH4 type or Alstom FP series sulfur hexafluoride circuit breaker to meet the needs of different users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;★ The combined valve can be opened flexibly. As the circuit breaker is pulled out, the valve will automatically close and be locked forcibly, eliminating the danger of accidental contact with high-voltage electricity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;★ The friendly man-machine interface makes the operation of the switch cabinet programmatic and formulaic, and the operator can understand it at a glance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;★ There are more than 160 main wiring schemes, and the structure is highly adaptable to meet the needs of different users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rated voltage: 24kV&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Power frequency withstand voltage: 50/65kV&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lightning impulse withstand voltage: 125kV&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated frequency: 50/60Hz&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Circuit breaker, branch bus rated current: 3150A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated peak withstand current: 40 kA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated short-circuit breaking current: 40 kA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated short-time withstand current: 4s&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: The external temperature is 55°C and the rated current is 2500A, forced ventilation is required!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Normal use conditions:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;normal-use-conditions&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#normal-use-conditions&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;◆Ambient air temperature: upper limit temperature +40℃. The lower limit temperature is -15°C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Relative humidity: daily average relative humidity: ≤95%; daily average water vapor pressure not exceeding 2.2KPa; monthly average relative humidity: ≤90%; monthly average water vapor pressure not exceeding 1.8KPa;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Altitude: below 1000m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Earthquake intensity: no more than 8℃.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆The surrounding air should be free from obvious pollution such as corrosive or combustible gas and water vapor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆No place with severe vibration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆When it is used under the normal conditions specified in GB3906, the user shall negotiate with the company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sales@lyskjd.com&#34; &gt;Sales@lyskjd.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KYN61 40.5 armored mobile AC metal enclosed switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/kyn61-40.5-armored-mobile-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/kyn61-40.5-armored-mobile-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/34.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;KYN61-40.5-armored-mobile-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KYN61-40.5(Z) armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear is suitable for power systems with a frequency of 50Hz, a rated voltage of 40.5kV and a rated current of up to 3150A. It has the functions of control, protection and monitoring of the circuit. Can be widely used in general power systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KYN61-40.5(Z) type armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear (hereinafter referred to as &amp;ldquo;switchgear&amp;rdquo;) is suitable for three-phase AC 5 0 Hz power systems, used in power plants, substations and industrial and mining enterprises The power distribution room is used to receive and distribute electric energy, and to control, protect and monitor the circuit.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/33.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;KYN61-40.5-armored-mobile-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This product meets the standards: GB3906 &amp;ldquo;3~35kV AC metal-enclosed switchgear&amp;rdquo;, GB/T11022 &amp;ldquo;High-voltage switchgear and control equipment standard common technical requirements&amp;rdquo;, IEC60298 &amp;ldquo;rated voltage above 1kV and below 50kV AC metal-enclosed switchgear and control equipment &amp;ldquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Integrated, miniaturized, and modularized product development with wide applicability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Five-defense&amp;rdquo; locking device design, safe and reliable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet has strong anti-corrosion and anti-oxidation properties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adopt balanced electric field measures, and the busbar is insulated with heat-shrinkable material, which has high insulation performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protection level can reach IP4X.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ambient air temperature: upper limit temperature +40°C. The lower limit temperature is -15°C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Relative humidity: daily average relative humidity: ≤95%, daily average water vapor pressure not exceeding 2.2KPa; monthly average relative humidity: ≤90%, monthly average water vapor pressure not exceeding 1.8KPa;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Altitude: below 1000m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earthquake intensity: no more than 8°C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The surrounding air should not be significantly polluted by corrosive or combustible gases, water vapor, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No place with severe vibration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it is used under the normal conditions specified in GB3906, it shall be negotiated by the user and the manufacturer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sales@lyskjd.com&#34; &gt;Sales@lyskjd.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LKGK 12 fully enclosed inflatable cabinet</title>
      <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/lkgk-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/lkgk-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/3.png&#34; alt=&#34;LKGK-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
LCGK-12 fully insulated and fully enclosed inflatable metal switchgear (referred to as inflatable cabinet) is also known as common box type inflatable cabinet, sf6 inflatable cabinet. All its live parts are completely sealed in a 3.0mm thick stainless steel SF6 gas box, multiple branch switches can be installed in one gas box, so that the switchgear is not affected by the environment. It truly realizes functions such as maintenance-free, reliable operation, and unattended operation. The inflatable cabinet unit adopts a modular design, which can be flexibly expanded and scientifically combined. It is a fully insulated and fully enclosed high-voltage switchgear. It is suitable for 50HZ, 12kv three-phase AC high-voltage power distribution system for receiving and distributing high-voltage electric energy. Because of its strong adaptability, it is widely used in mines, coastal areas, alpine plateau areas, airports, hotels, schools, subways, municipal construction and other industries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fully insulated and fully enclosed, all live equipment in the inflatable cabinet is encapsulated in a stainless steel gas box, and the outgoing cables are connected by closed cable plugs, which can effectively isolate the environmental impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The inflatable cabinet adopts a modular design, which can flexibly expand the unit, while occupying an area of more than 50% less than that of conventional high-voltage switch cabinets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protection level of the shell is high. The gas box of the inflatable cabinet is made of 3.0mm thick stainless steel plate welded by a welding robot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The inflatable cabinet can choose electric operation or manual operation, and at the same time realize the remote monitoring function, with a high degree of intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The main technical parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;the-main-technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#the-main-technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflatable cabinet is a full name. It includes all unit cabinets. Commonly used are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unit C: load switch module. It is equivalent to the incoming line of the ring network cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;F unit: load switch fuse combination module. Equivalent to the outgoing line of the ring network cabinet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;V unit: Vacuum switch module. Equivalent to a circuit breaker unit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unit D: Cable connection module without grounding knife. Equivalent to a lift cabinet unit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sales@lyskjd.com&#34; &gt;Sales@lyskjd.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TBB10 High Voltage Collective Compensation Device</title>
      <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/tbb-10-high-voltage-collective-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/tbb-10-high-voltage-collective-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/44.png&#34; alt=&#34;TBB-10-High-Voltage-Collective-Compensation-Device&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
The TBB□-10 high-voltage collective compensation device mainly avoids the disadvantages of large local compensation investment, equipment maintenance, and decentralized operation management. The centralized compensation device is mainly used in 3-10kV three-phase power frequency AC power system with small load changes. in the power system. The high-voltage reactive power centralized compensation device can compensate the reactive power required by the system online, so that the reactive power of the system can reach a static balance, so as to improve the power factor of the system, stabilize the system voltage, reduce losses, and save electricity costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The device is equipped with a series air-core reactor with a reactance rate of 0.5%-12%, which can suppress the fifth and above harmonics and limit the closing inrush current. The reactance rate can be configured according to user requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The whole device adopts a frame structure, which is compact in structure, easy to install and maintain, and is equipped with safety measures of high-voltage live forced locking, which can ensure the personal safety of maintenance and operation personnel; it can ensure the safe operation of the equipment under the best environmental conditions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The main technical parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;the-main-technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#the-main-technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rated voltage: 3kV, 6kV, 10kV, 24kV, 35kV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Power frequency: 50Hz/60Hz.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Power factor: can reach above 0.95.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Residual voltage: 3 minutes after the power is disconnected, it can drop below sov.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sales@lyskjd.com&#34; &gt;Sales@lyskjd.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TBB10 High Voltage Reactive Power Automatic Compensation Device</title>
      <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/7.png&#34; alt=&#34;TBB-10-High-Voltage-Reactive-Power-Automatic-Compensation-Device&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
TBB□-10 high-voltage reactive power automatic compensation device is suitable for reactive power automatic tracking compensation of 35kV, 10kV (6kV) buses in 220kV, 110kV, 35kV substations, and is mainly used in 3-35kV three-phase power frequency AC power systems with large load fluctuations , the use of centralized compensation still cannot meet the system requirements, often resulting in over-compensation or under-compensation. This device can detect the reactive power required by the system in real time, and then compare it with the set value to perform automatic intelligent switching operation, so that the reactive power of the system can reach a dynamic balance, so as to improve the power factor of the system and stabilize the system Voltage, reduce loss and save electricity cost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equipped with ZKG or GKN type controller, the power factor and system voltage can be controlled within the set range by automatically tracking the switching capacitor and controlling the on-load voltage regulation of the main transformer. It can automatically identify and adapt to various operation modes of dual main substations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through the remote automatic selection switch, various working modes of voltage regulation and compensation can be flexibly selected&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It can automatically identify and display the position information of the pressure regulating switch through BCD code or one-to-one correspondence. It has control and protection functions such as synchronous adjustment of the voltage regulation gears of the two main transformers, anti-skid gears, and light gas alarm lockout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Real-time display of main transformer low-voltage side voltage, current, power factor, reactive power, capacitor switching status and alarm protection information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has the function of harmonic measurement and display, which can measure and display the high-order harmonic content of the low-voltage measurement current in real time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has alarm protection functions such as high voltage, low voltage, PT disconnection, structural failure, and main transformer overcurrent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Equipped with RS-485 or RS-232 high-speed data communication interface, it can realize the &amp;ldquo;four remote&amp;rdquo; function by cooperating with the integrated automation system of the main substation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The high-voltage vacuum switch dedicated to modular capacitors is used, and five sets are installed in one side of the ordinary switch cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It can be flexibly grouped according to the total compensation capacity, and can be divided into 6 groups with different capacities at most, and the maximum capacity of each group is 2000Kvar/5000Kvar, and it can be switched automatically according to the combination of reactive power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Equipped with ZSBH capacitor bank microcomputer protection device can realize two-stage overcurrent and zero-sequence voltage protection functions. When a failure occurs in a certain group, Ke will automatically cut off and block, without affecting the normal switching of other capacitor groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reactors with different ratios are configured to limit the closing inrush current and suppress high-order harmonics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Ordering Information:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;ordering-information&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#ordering-information&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Main circuit scheme number, purpose, single-line system diagram, arrangement diagram and distribution room layout diagram, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Auxiliary circuit wiring schematic diagram and terminal arrangement diagram.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The type, specification and quantity of the electrical components in the switchgear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The switchgear control room or the incoming cabinet needs to be connected by a bus bridge, and the rated carrying capacity of the bus bridge, the span of the bus bridge, and the height from the ground should be provided with specific requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When accessories and spare parts are needed, the type and quantity should be proposed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The switchgear is used in special environmental conditions, which should be specified when ordering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sales@lyskjd.com&#34; &gt;Sales@lyskjd.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XGN15 24 AC high voltage hexafluoride flow ring network switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/xgn15-24-ac-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/xgn15-24-ac-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/30.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;XGN15-24-AC-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;XGN15-24 AC high-voltage sulfur hexafluoride ring network switchgear (hereinafter referred to as ring network cabinet) is a new generation of high-voltage electrical products successfully researched by our company by introducing foreign advanced technology and in accordance with the requirements of domestic home appliances and urban network transformation. Strict form test and long-term trial operation assessment, all technical performance indicators have reached the national inspection standards. The main switch, operating mechanism and components of the unit cabinet adopt the FLN36-24 type SF6 switchgear independently produced by Daya Electric Group, and its operation mode is divided into manual and automatic. Can fully meet the changing needs of the market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;XGN15-24 unit type sulfur hexafluoride ring network cabinet is suitable for AC 50Hz, 24kV power system, widely used in industrial and civil cable ring network and power supply terminal projects. Especially suitable for the following places: power distribution in urban residential areas, small secondary substations, switching stations, industrial and mining enterprises, shopping malls, airports, subways, wind power stadiums, railways, tunnels, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Altitude 1000m; (If you have special requirements, please specify when ordering)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ambient temperature: -35+40&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The average daily relative humidity does not exceed 95%; the average monthly relative humidity does not exceed 90%;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shock resistance: 8 degrees&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No violent vibration and impact, and places with fire, chemical corrosion, and danger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sales@lyskjd.com&#34; &gt;Sales@lyskjd.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XGN66 12 type fixed closed switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/xgn66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/xgn66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/27.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;XGN66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;XGN66-12(Z) box-type fixed AC metal-enclosed switchgear (referred to as &amp;ldquo;switchgear&amp;rdquo;), this product is suitable for power single busbars with a rated voltage of 3.6-12kv, three-phase AC 50hz, and a rated current of 630A-3150A. Double busbar and single busbar with bypass system are used for receiving and distributing electric energy. It can meet the requirements of various types of power plants, substations (stations) and industrial and mining enterprises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;XGN66-12(Z) switchgear is a metal-enclosed box-type structure. The frame of the cabinet is welded by angle steel. The cabinet is divided into a circuit breaker room, a busbar room, a cable room, a relay room, etc., and the rooms are separated by steel plates. open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The circuit breaker room is in the front lower part of the cabinet, the rotation of the circuit breaker is connected with the operating mechanism by the pull rod, the upper terminal of the circuit breaker is connected with the upper isolating switch, the lower terminal of the circuit breaker is connected with the current transformer, and the current transformer is connected with the lower isolating switch The circuit breaker is also equipped with a pressure release channel. If an internal arc occurs, the gas can release the pressure through the exhaust channel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The busbar room is at the rear upper part of the cabinet body. In order to reduce the height of the cabinet body, the busbars are in the shape of a row and supported by qualified insulators with a bending strength of 12kn. The busbars are connected to the busbars of the upper disconnector. isolation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cable room is behind the lower part of the cabinet. The supporting insulator in the cable room can be equipped with a voltage monitoring device, and the cables are fixed on the bracket. When the main connection line is the connection scheme, this room is the connection room. The relay room is in front of the upper part of the cabinet. Various relays can be installed on the indoor installation board. There are terminal block brackets in the room. Secondary components such as indicating instruments and signal components can be installed on the door. Secondary small busbars can also be arranged on the top.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The operating mechanism of the circuit breaker is at the lower left position, and above it is the operation and interlocking mechanism of the isolating switch. The switch cabinet is double-sided maintenance, the secondary components of the relay room are inspected at the front, the operating mechanism, mechanical interlock and transmission part are maintained, and the circuit breaker is inspected. The main busbar and cable terminals are maintained at the back, and lighting lamps are installed in the circuit breaker room. Below the front door, there is a grounding copper bus bar parallel to the cabinet width direction, with a cross-section of 4*40mm².&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mechanical interlock: In order to prevent opening and closing of the isolating switch with load, prevent mis-opening and closing of the circuit breaker, prevent mistakenly entering the charged interval, prevent the grounding switch from being charged, and prevent the closing of the switch with a grounding knife, the switch cabinet adopts a corresponding mechanical interlock. The action principle of the interlock is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Power failure operation (operation-inspection)&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;power-failure-operation-operation-inspection&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#power-failure-operation-operation-inspection&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The switchgear is in the working position, that is, the upper and lower isolating switches, the circuit breaker is in the closed state, the front and rear doors are locked, and it is in the electric operation. At this time, the small handle is in the working position. First open the circuit breaker, and then pull the small handle to the &amp;ldquo;break lock&amp;rdquo; position. At this time, the circuit breaker cannot be closed. Insert the operating handle into the operation hole of the lower isolation and pull it down from top to bottom. Take off the handle, insert it into the operating hole of the upper isolation, pull it down from the top, and pull it to the opening position of the upper isolation, then take down the operating handle, insert it into the operating hole of the grounding switch, and push it from bottom to top, so that the grounding switch is in the closing position. position, at this time, the small handle can be placed in the &amp;ldquo;inspection&amp;rdquo; position. The front door can be opened first, and the key behind the door can be taken out to open the back door. After the power failure operation is completed, the maintenance personnel can enter and maintain the circuit breaker room and the cable room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Transmission operation (overhaul - operation)&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;transmission-operation-overhaul---operation&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#transmission-operation-overhaul---operation&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the overhaul is completed and power needs to be transmitted, the operation procedure is as follows: close the back door, take out the key and close the front door, and turn the small handle from the &amp;ldquo;inspection&amp;rdquo; position to the &amp;ldquo;break lock&amp;rdquo; position. At this time, the front door is locked and the circuit breaker cannot be closed. Insert the operating handle into the operating hole of the grounding switch, pull it from top to bottom, make the grounding switch in the opening position, take down the operating handle, insert it into the operating hole of the upper isolation, and push it from bottom to upper, so that the upper isolation is in the closing position. In the brake position, take down the operating handle, insert it into the operating hole of the lower isolation, push it from bottom to upper, so that the lower isolation is in the closing position, take out the operating handle, and pull the small handle to the working position, then the circuit breaker can be closed .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Normal use conditions:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;normal-use-conditions&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#normal-use-conditions&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;◆The altitude does not exceed 1000m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Ambient temperature: -25℃～+40℃, the average temperature within 24 hours does not exceed +35℃.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆The horizontal inclination is not more than 3°C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Seismic intensity does not exceed 8℃.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆No severe vibration, shock and explosion hazard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sales@lyskjd.com&#34; &gt;Sales@lyskjd.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XGN68 12 indoor AC box type metal enclosed switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/xgn68-12-indoor-ac-box-type-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.lyskjd.com/en/products/high-voltage-switchgear-cabinet/xgn68-12-indoor-ac-box-type-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/26.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;XGN68-12-indoor-AC-box-type-metal-enclosed-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;XGN68-12(F), XGN68-12(F.R), XGN68-12(Z) box-type (indoor) AC metal-enclosed switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear) is a new generation of complete sets of high-voltage electrical appliances of our company. Adopting foreign advanced technology, it is small in size, only 50% of the volume of ordinary switch cabinets; the circuit breaker has high reliability and good performance; the &amp;ldquo;five-proof&amp;rdquo; interlocking mechanism is reliable and simple. The switchgear is a 3.6, 7.2, 12KV three-phase AC 50Hz single-bus section indoor complete device for receiving and distributing electric energy. It also has the functions of controlling, protecting and monitoring circuits, and can be used in various types of power plants, substations, industrial and mining enterprises, high-rise buildings, etc., and can also be combined with ring main units in switching stations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ZN100-12 vacuum circuit breaker and FZN58-12 vacuum load switch used in the XGN68-12 switchgear adopt vacuum arc chamber epoxy resin sealing technology, which has beautiful appearance, good insulation performance and convenient operation. The design of the rotating fuse structure is adopted in the cabinet, so that the replacement of the fuse can be realized It has beautiful appearance, good insulation performance and convenient operation. The designed rotating fuse structure is adopted in the cabinet, which makes the replacement of the fuse realize the draw-out type, which is very convenient. Pull-out type, very convenient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet body is welded with high-quality angle steel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The circuit breaker room is located in the middle (lower) part of the cabinet, which is convenient for installation, debugging and maintenance. Equipped with ZN63A (VS1-12) circuit breaker as standard, and equipped with a pressure release channel to ensure personal safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The advanced and reliable rotary isolating switch can be used to safely enter the circuit breaker room for inspection and maintenance when the main busbar is live.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protection level of the whole cabinet is IP2X.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Equipped with a reliable and fully functional compulsory mechanical locking device, which is simple and effective to meet the requirements of &amp;ldquo;five defenses&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have a reliable grounding system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is an observation window on the door, which can clearly observe the working status of the components in the cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The locking mechanism of the operating mechanism adopts the JSXGN locking mechanism used in the XGN2-12 cabinet, which is simple, reliable, convenient and practical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The incoming and outgoing cables are lower than the front of the cabinet bottom, which is convenient for users to connect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lyskjd.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Sales@lyskjd.com&#34; &gt;Sales@lyskjd.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
